Hello friends, I welcome to the channel,
today I am telling you how to register a claim. There are
two processes for registering a claim. One, you can register your claim through a toll free number
and the second is through the website.
I am telling you
how the website was started from the beginning. It is a very
simple method.
This is their claim registration form. Whatever
you tell at the time of registration,
you have to fill the same form. First,
we will tell you how to register.
You
can do it very easily online through the website and the toll free
number takes some time but it can be done on that too.
You have to tell the details. There is
also an assistant there who helps you
file this up. You have to file it up through this process and
register the file. And
see here it is written that
after clicking here, customers can make a claim.
Click here and see, when we click on this,
a pop opens in front of you.
What do you have to do?
Click here. Click there.
See, after opening the browser, click there
for the intimation.  The
policy number is written in the entry. Now what will we do, this policy number is
given on the policy, see
here it is given on the policy
3205506744, we will dial this number and
note it down, what will happen after you
confirm it, so after confirming it, there are
three steps in this
[music]
where the car is parked, give its name, the
date of the accident has to be filled there, after that the time of accident, at
which time this accident happened,
this has to be filled, after that the P code
which is given on your policy number has to be
filled here and it will be automatically filled, your
form which is already there,
which city is there,
you just have to fill in which India the incident happened,
so we will dial the P code here,
dial this P code, this form of yours is
already there, where is it from,
after that we will enter the area here, where did
this incident happen, whatever
happened in the CD, we will enter the city here,
after that see, here it is at which place
in your car
After the damage, in the supplementary, what was
damaged or stolen, then this is filled,
after that you have to
write a short description of how this vehicle fell
due to which the vehicle fell while trying to save the animal, confirm continue,
okay, after that it comes,
okay then yes
[sangeet]
[sangeet] will
check out, so see here, claim
registration
[sangeet] will be
made or vehicle number will be made, well
this number is, we will
fill the address, we will give mobile number, we will put t and p,
after that in the second, time incident
and date and which field has to be filled, after that
in type of, we will put online match online
description, there we will
leave commercial vehicle and then it will leave
its driver details,
you will fill it with driver license
and here we will fill the date and pre in advance
and sign, so if you like the video, then
subscribe to my channel,
comment and write in the comment area
which topic video you want, thank you
friend